// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "ISO 9126 Quality Factors are,",
  answer: "All of the mentioned above",
  options: [
    "Functionality, Reliability  ",
    "Usability, Efficiency",
    "Maintainability, Portability",
    "All of the mentioned above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Software security provides ___ that enable a software system to protect its assets from attack.",
  answer: "The mechanisms",
  options: [
    "The mechanisms",
    "The ability to product",
    "The software process",
    "None of the mentioned above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Security assurance is preformed and continues throughout ____.",
  answer: "None of the mentioned above",
  options: [
    "The hardware process",
    "The software process",
    "The hardware & software both",
    "None of the mentioned above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "  Software security is an aspect of software ____.",
  answer: "Quality assurance",
  options: [
    "Process assurance",
    "Quality assurance",
    "Product assurance",
    "All of the mentioned above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Security is not just a concern to the people developing software for ____." ,
  answer: "All of the mentioned above",
  options: [
    "The military",
    "Government",
    "Health agencies",
    "All of the mentioned above",

    
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: " Cloud computing brings additional ___ and ___ concerns." ,
  answer: "Confidentiality, privacy",
  options: [
    "Confidentiality, privacy",
    "Testing, development",
    "Integration, maintenance",
    "All of the mentioned above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Amongst which of the following is / are the security case consists elements," ,
  answer: "All of the mentioned above",
  options: [
    "The claims themselves",
    "The arguments that link the claims to each other through evidence and assumptions",
    "The body of evidence and explicit assumptions that support the arguments.",
    "All of the mentioned above"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: "When software design patterns are considered, we strive to identify and ____." ,
  answer: "Document generative patterns",
  options: [
    "Document generative patterns",
    "System patterns",
    "Network system",
    "None of the mentioned above"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Architectural patterns describe broad-based design problems that are solved using a ___ approach."  ,
  answer: "Structural",
  options: [
    "Unstructured",
    "Structural",
    "All of the mentioned above",
    "Semi-structural"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Component patterns also referred to as design patterns address problems associated with the development of ____. " ,
  answer: "	Subsystems and components",
  options: [
    "Subsystems and components",
    "System implementation",
    "System integration",
    "All of the mentioned above"
  ]
},



// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];